How did viewing a diff between two versions of a file help you see the bug that
was introduced?

    It helped me to understand what a bug is and how it can affect a working code.

How could having easy access to the entire history of a file make you a more
efficient programmer in the long term?

    If I have access to the history, I won't loose time with looking for the old versions and I can come back from big mistakes or complicated bugs. 

What do you think are the pros and cons of manually choosing when to create a
commit, like you do in Git, vs having versions automatically saved, like Google
docs does?

    One con is forgetting to commit. One pro is to have full control over the commit messages. 

Why do you think some version control systems, like Git, allow saving multiple
files in one commit, while others, like Google Docs, treat each file separately?

    I think Git is a tool for software developers. A programming project includes many files and if we had to commit one file at a time, it wouldn't be time efficient nor easy to use. Also it is easy to forget to commit some of the files we didn't touch.That would cause errors. 

How can you use the commands git log and git diff to view the history of files?

    Git log shows you the stages of the files. git diff runs on the commited files and shows the difference in the content of the files.

How might using version control make you more confident to make changes that
could break something?

    When use git, you always have a working copy. You can always try a new thing without worrying about breaking the code. 

Now that you have your workspace set up, what do you want to try using Git for?

    To keep versions of my files!